window.QUIZ_NUMERAL = {
    "title":"Arabic Numerals",
    "version":1,
    "count":10,
    "questions":
    [
        {"id":1,"question":"(واحِدٌ) ١","options":["Two","One","Seven","Five"],"answer":"One","answer_index":1},
        {"id":2,"question":"(اِثنانِ) ٢","options":["Four","Three","Two","Eight"],"answer":"Two","answer_index":2},
        {"id":3,"question":"(ثَلاثَةٌ) ٣","options":["Six","Three","Nine","One"],"answer":"Three","answer_index":1},
        {"id":4,"question":"(أربَعَةٌ) ٤","options":["Five","Four","Two","Ten"],"answer":"Four","answer_index":1},
        {"id":5,"question":"(خَمسَةٌ) ٥","options":["Seven","Eight","Five","Three"],"answer":"Five","answer_index":2},
        {"id":6,"question":"(سِتَّةٌ) ٦","options":["Six","Four","Nine","One"],"answer":"Six","answer_index":0},
        {"id":7,"question":"(سَبعَةٌ) ٧","options":["Five","Seven","Six","Two"],"answer":"Seven","answer_index":1},
        {"id":8,"question":"(ثَمانِيَةٌ) ٨","options":["Eight","Ten","Three","Six"],"answer":"Eight","answer_index":0},
        {"id":9,"question":"(تِسعَةٌ) ٩","options":["Seven","Nine","Four","One"],"answer":"Nine","answer_index":1},
        {"id":10,"question":"(عَشَرَةٌ) ١٠","options":["Ten","Eight","Five","Nine"],"answer":"Ten","answer_index":0}
    ]
};
